

shana SANDERS

www.coderfoundry.com/shanasanders

FRAMEWORKS & PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

HTML5 CSS3 JavaScript JQuery Bootstrap .NET C# MVC ASP.NET SQL LINQ

Xamarin WebAPI

CODER

1231 Shields Road, Suite 5 Kernersville, NC 27284 (336) 231-8632

partnerships@coderfoundry.com

This resume contains information furnished by the candidate and has not been independently verified by Coder Foundry, LLC.

This information is privileged, confidential, and to be used solely by the individual and entity to which it has been submitted.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Coder Foundry, Web Software Engineer

Kernersville, NC · February 2018-April 2018

- Created a personal portfolio utilizing C#, MVC, HTML5, CSS3, BOOTSTRAP, JS & jQuery. Additionally, enhanced the site with a blog and developed the database using Code First Migrations with LINQ and Entity Framework. Additional technologies: CK Editor, Syntax Highlighter.
- Fully designed and developed a multi-functional project/issue tracker web application, implementing enhanced roles & security along with file uploading features. Code First Relational database designed and modeled in SQL Server. Technologies used include: .Net Framework v. 4.6.1, MVC6, C#, LINQ, SQL, Entity Framework, jQuery DataTables.

Southern Grace Salon, Hair Stylist

Thomasville, NC · 2017–2018

- Maintained quality service by following organization standards.
- Contributed to team effort by accomplishing related results as needed.
- Ensured appropriate cleanliness of work areas.
- Provided full salon services, including hair cutting, shampooing, blow drying, coloring and styling.
- Collected payments for salon services performed.
- **Skills/Qualifications:** Listening, Supply Management, Analyzing Information, Customer Focus, Client Relationships, Organization, Creativity, Attention to Detail, Confidentiality, Professionalism, Verbal Communication

EDUCATION

Health and Style Institute, General Cosmetology/Cosmetologist *Greensboro*, NC · 2016–2017